http://www.darecapital.com/privacy-policy

Home, Who We Are, What We Do, Will's Market Letter, Contact Info, Links, Brochure, Privacy Policy
Privacy policy
Privacy PolicyWhat does dare capital management, LLC do with your personal information?DCM, LLC may collect personal information from our clients in order to understand, recommend, and implement financial decisions with the help of and on behalf of our clients. That information may include: Name, address, email address, phone number Date of birth, spousal info, dependent info Social Security number and financial account numbers  Account balances and transaction information  Income and employment information  Trust and estate planning documents The information that is collected may be used to discuss and implement tax planning, investment management, retirement planning, estate planning, budgeting/cash management, and/or risk management strategies on behalf of the client and/or the client’s family. If client authorizes it, non-public information may be forwarded to TD Ameritrade Institutional or another custodian for the purposes of assisting the client in establishing investment or retirement accounts. If the client authorizes it, non-public information may also be forwarded to accountants or other professional services firms with whom the client has a business relationship for the purposes of tax preparation or estate planning. Dare Capital Management does not share any non-public client information except as required by law. Dare Capital Management uses computer safeguards and secured office access to protect client information from unauthorized access. About darecapital.com The Dare Capital.com website does not collect visitor information except that which is supplied by visitors wishing to be contacted on the contact form. The information is only used to contact the party making the inquiry. Information provided by interested parties on the darecapital.com website will not be knowingly disseminated to any third party for any reason. Updated 8/12/202405 S. Croatan Hwy, Suite C
P.O. Box 1806Nags Head, NC 27959 (252) 480-0156 www.darecapital.com
©2020 DCM, LLC ALL RIGHTS RESERVED
Back to Top
2405-C S. Croatan Hwy., PO Box 1806, Nags Head, NC 27959, USA252-480-0156will@darecapital.com
